<?xml version="1.0" ?>

<documentations>
	<documentation>
		<name>booster</name>
		<title>Booster</title>
		<text>At the booster the pulse is amplified the first time. Everytime the pulse passes the red titanium-sapphirine crystal in the middle more energy is transferred.</text>
	</documentation>
	<documentation>
		<name>compressor</name>
		<title>Compressor</title>
		<text>Only in vacuo the pulse can be shortenend or compressed to its originally length, because air would get ionised from it. The compression happens reverse to the pulse stretching.</text>
	</documentation>
	<documentation>
		<name>multipassI</name>
		<title>1st Multipass</title>
		<text>The pulse is now scales bigger than at the beginning. With this length it can be amplified further without risc.</text>
	</documentation>
	<documentation>
		<name>multipassII</name>
		<title>2nd Multipass</title>
		<text>Now the pulse a amplified the second time. The light pulse is already so intense, that the amplifying crystal has to be cooled down. For the further amplification the laser beam diameter has to be increased.</text>
	</documentation>
	<documentation>
		<name>multipassIII</name>
		<title>3rd Multipass</title>
		<text>In the last amplifier the pulse gets its final enery. The energy is added by a pump laser. To do this efficient the amplifying crystal have to be cooled down to -100 degree Celsius.</text>
	</documentation>
	<documentation>
		<name>oscillator</name>
		<title>Master Oscillator</title>
		<text>The laser pulse leaves the master oscillator, a femtosecondlaser. Here it has only one hundredmillionionth of its end energy.</text>
	</documentation>
	<documentation>
		<name>reg_amplifier</name>
		<title>Regenerative Amplifier</title>
		<text>The pulse enlargement happend in the grating stretcher. The different wave lengths of the pulses take different long pathes, so the pulse become longer altogether.</text>
	</documentation>
	<documentation>
		<name>stretcher</name>
		<title>Stretcher</title>
		<text>To amplify the pulse further it has to elongated now. Otherweise it would be so intense, that it would destroy the mirrors with further amplification.</text>
	</documentation>
</documentations>