<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<helps>
	<help id="Draco">
		<name>Draco</name>
		<text>This is the room where the laser is created and magnified. Feel free to alter the laser's speed and the light intensity. The laser's energy is displayed as it traverses the system. You may pause and stop the animation at any time. You can click elements of the system to display a short description of the components. Free View will let you roam freely through the room. Orbit View will let you follow the laser on it's path through the system. Tour View will give you an overview of the system.</text>
	</help>
	<help id="Draco_d">
		<name>Draco_d</name>
		<text>In diesem Raum wird der Laserimpuls erzeugt und vergrößert.&#10;Sie können die Geschwindigkeit der Simulation und die Raumhelligkeit einstellen. Die Laserenergie in den verschiedenen Modulen wird unten angezeigt. Sie können die Animation auch jederzeit unterbrechen oder stoppen. Mit "Freie Sicht" können Sie sich mittels WASD frei im Raum bewegen. Mit der Orbitsicht folgen sie dem Laserpuls durch den Aufbau. Zoomen Sie mit dem Mausrad ran, um mehr Details wahrzunehmen. Mit der Toursicht folgt die Kamera dem Laser in einem modulumfassenden Abstand.</text>
	</help>
	<help id="Elbe">
		<name>Elbe</name>
		<text>This is the room where electrons are created and bundled into a bunch. Feel free to alter the bunch's speed. You may pause and stop the animation at any time. You can click elements of the system to display a short description of the component along with a picture. Free View will let you roam freely through the room. Follow Electron will let you follow the bunch on it's path through the system. You can open and close the covers of the configuration by clicking Show/Hide Cover. Options will let you manipulate a variety of values that correspond with the bunch's behavior inside the system. With "save log.txt" you save the whole way of a bunch to the file log.txt. If the simulation is too slow try to deactivate the field arrows. Furthermore you can save or load your settings.</text>
	</help>
	<help id="Elbe_d">
		<name>Elbe_d</name>
		<text>Im Elberaum werden riesige Elektronenbündel erstellt. Sie können die Animationsgeschwindigkeit einstellen oder die Simualtion pausieren oder stoppen. Weiterhin können Sie die meisten Geräte sehr detailiert einstellen. Für die konkreten Module stehen eigene Hilfetexte zur Verfügung. Mit der "freien Sicht" können Sie mittels WASD frei im Raum umherlaufen. In der Orbitsicht folgen Sie einem Elektronenbündel. Desweiteren können Sie mit dem Button "Hülle" die Ummantelung anzeigen oder deaktiven. Rechts gibt es zwei Buttons ("RF Einst." und "Magnet Einst.") für eine zentrale Einstellung alles Bauteile, welche aber auch durch Klick auf selbige justiert werden können. Mit "log.txt speichern" lassen Sie ein Bündel fliegen und eine log.txt wird erstellt, welche alle Positionen auf dem Weg mitlogt. Sollte die Simulation zu langsam werden, können Sie die Feldpfeile deaktivieren, um Ressourcen zu sparen. Außerdem kann man die gemachten Einstellungen laden oder speichern.</text>
	</help>
	<help id="Collision">
		<name>Collision</name>
		<text>This is the room where the collision of electrons and the laser takes place.&#10;If you approach the bunch close enough you can see individual electrons and eventually the field lines of an electron.&#10;Feel free to alter the bunch's and the laser's speed, the length of the field lines, the time per step and the slow motion factor. You may pause and stop the animation at any time.&#10;Free View will let you roam freely through the room. Follow Electron will fix the camera onto the bunch.&#10;You can hide/unhide both the cover of the configuration by clicking Hide Cover and the path that the electrons and the laser take by clicking Hide Path.&#10;Press F3 to hide/unhide the GUI.</text>
	</help>
	<help id="Collision_d">
		<name>Collision</name>
		<text>Dit muss deutsch! This is the room where the collision of electrons and the laser takes place.&#10;If you approach the bunch close enough you can see individual electrons and eventually the field lines of an electron.&#10;Feel free to alter the bunch's and the laser's speed, the length of the field lines, the time per step and the slow motion factor. You may pause and stop the animation at any time.&#10;Free View will let you roam freely through the room. Follow Electron will fix the camera onto the bunch.&#10;You can hide/unhide both the cover of the configuration by clicking Hide Cover and the path that the electrons and the laser take by clicking Hide Path.&#10;Press F3 to hide/unhide the GUI.</text>
	</help>
	<help id="Radiation">
		<name>Radiation 3D</name>
		<text>This state will let you see what happens to a single electron when it is hit by the laser.&#10;You can manipulate a variety of values.&#10;&#10;ATTENTION! Increasing the length of the field lines will cost a lot of performance. Please adjust according to your computer's power.&#10;Press F3 to hide/unhide the GUI.</text>
	</help>
	<help id="Radiation_d">
		<name>Radiation 3D</name>
		<text>Dit muss deutsch! This state will let you see what happens to a single electron when it is hit by the laser.&#10;You can manipulate a variety of values.&#10;&#10;ATTENTION! Increasing the length of the field lines will cost a lot of performance. Please adjust according to your computer's power.&#10;Press F3 to hide/unhide the GUI.</text>
	</help>
  <help id="Credits">
    <name>Credits</name>
    <text>Instructor: Prof. Dr. Stefan Gumhold&#10;Tutor: Dr. Niels von Festenberg&#10;Team members: Johannes Völker, Stefan Wagner, Annett Ungethüm, Alexander Matthes, Benjamin Schneider, Tino Helmig&#10;Helmholtz-Zentrum Dresden-Rossendorf: Alexander Debus, Michael Bussmann, Fabian Röser, Andre Arnold&#10;Draco team members: Tobias Günther, Sebastian Hagedorn, Sebastian von Hippel, Alexander Manger, Mathias Müller, Christian Schubert, Sebastian Walther, Tino Winkler&#10;Elbe team members: Mathieu Floira, Timon Bätz, René Lützner, Florian Klopfleisch, Sebastian Walther</text>
  </help>
</helps>
